Guide to the Arthur Levitt, Jr. Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III: Speeches and Testimonies
  - Subseries III.1: SEC Speeches
    - Remarks: Lawyers And Ethics: The Problem of Pay-to-Playat the Fixed Income Daily Conference on Municipal Finance, Philadelphia, PA, June 26, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Remarks: Fulfilling the Promise of Disclosure at the American Savings Education Council, New York, NY, July 23, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Remarks: Investing Wisely: Tips From an SEC insider at the Investors' Town Meeting, Union Performing Arts Center, Tulsa, OK, August 4, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Remarks concerning pay-to-play to the American Bar Association, House of Delegates, San Francisco, CA, August 6, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Remarks: The Importance of High Quality Accounting Standards at the Inter-American Development Bank, Washington, DC, September 29, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Remarks: A Declaration of Accounting Independenceto The Conference Board, New York, NY, October 8, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Remarks: The Risks and Rewards of Technology to the International Federation of Stock Exchanges, New York, NY, October 13, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Welcoming Remarks to SEC's Consumer Affairs Advisory Committee, Washington, DC, October 14, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Remarks: A Renewed Precedent: The Securities Bar and the SEC to the Practicing Law Institute, 29th Annual Institute on Securities Regulation, November 6, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Remarks to the Securities Industry Association, Boca Raton, FL, November 7, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Remarks: Investing Wisely: Tips From an SEC insider at the Investors' Town Meeting, Des Moines, IA, November 21, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Remarks: Inclusion and Diversity on Wall Streetto the Wall Street Project // Rainbow-PUSH Coalition, January 16, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Remarks: Technological Challenges for Modern Marketsto Women in Housing and Finance, Inc., January 21, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Remarks: Financial Self-Defense: Protection in the Modern Markets at the Investors' Town Meeting, Los Angeles, CA, February 8, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Remarks: Financial Self-Defense: Tips From an SEC insider at the Investors' Town Meeting, Palo Alto, CA, February 17, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Remarks: A Question of Integrity: Promoting Investor Confidence by Fighting Insider Trading to the S.E.C. SpeaksConference, Washington, DC, February 27, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Remarks: Investor Protection in the Age of Technologyat the Third Annual Financial Services and Technology Conference, Salt Lake City, UT, March 6, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Remarks: Corporate Governance: Integrity in the Information Age at the Tenth Annual Corporate Law Institute, Tulane University, New Orleans, LA, March 12, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Remarks to the National Roundtable on Saving and Investing, Facts on Saving and Investing Campaign, Federal Trade Commission, Washington, DC, March 30, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Remarks: The State of the Brokerage Profession before the Securities Industry Association's Legal and Compliance Seminar, Scottsdale, AZ, April 20, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Remarks: Reaching the Right Balance: Options for Innovative Marketson the Occasion of the 25th Anniversary of the Chicago Board Options Exchange and Options Clearing Corporation, Chicago, IL, April 24, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Remarks at the Enforcement Division Meeting, Solomon's Island, May 6, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Remarks at the Investment Company Institute, Washington, DC, May 15, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Remarks: Financial Self-Defense: Tips From an SEC insider at the Investors' Town Meeting, Bloomington, MN, June 1, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Remarks: Financial Self-Defense: Tips From an SEC insider at the Investors' Town Meeting, Bangor, ME, June 30, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Remarks: The Importance of Transparency In America's Debt Market at the Media Studies Center, New York, NY, September 9, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Remarks: The Numbers Game at the New York University Center for Law and Business, New York, NY, September 28, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Remarks: The SEC Perspective on Investing Social Security in the Stock Market at the John F. Kennedy School of Government Forum, Harvard University, Cambridge, MA, October 19, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Remarks: Meeting the Challenges of a 21st Century Marketplace at the Securities Industry Association Annual Meeting, Boca Raton, FL, November 6, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Remarks: A Financial Partnershipat the Financial Executives Institute, New York, NY, November 16, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Remarks: Expanding the Promise of Opportunity and Security Through Saving and Investing before the Consumer Federation of America, Washington, DC, December 3, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Remarks: A Partnership for the Public Trust at the American Institute of Certified Public Accountants (AICPA), Washington, DC, December 8, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Opening Remarks at the SEC Roundtable on the Role of Independent Investment Company Directors, Washington, DC, February 23, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Remarks: Financial Self-Defense: Tips From an SEC insider at the Miami Heralds First Annual Personal Finance Conference, Miami, FL, March 6, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Remarks to the Directors' College 1999, Stanford Law School, Stanford University, Stanford, CA, March 22, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Remarks: Keeping Faith with the Shareholder Interest: Strengthening the Role of Independent Directors of Mutual Funds at the Mutual Funds and Investment Management Conference, Palm Springs, CA, March 22, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Remarks: In the Best Interests of Beneficiaries: Trust and Public Funds at the 1999 Annual Meeting of the Council of Institutional Investors, Washington, DC, March 30, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Remarks Before the Securities Industry Association's Legal and Compliance Seminar, Boca Raton, FL, April 13, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Remarks at the 19th Annual Ray Garret, Jr. Corporate and Securities Law Institute, Northwestern Law School, April 22, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Remarks Before the Bond Market Association, San Francisco, CA, April 23, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Remarks: Financial Literacy and Role of the Mediaat the Media Studies Center, New York, NY, April 26, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Remarks: Plain Talk About On-Line Investingat the National Press Club, May 4, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Remarks to the Committee for Economic Development, New York, NY, May 19, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Remarks: Common Sense Investing in the 21st Century Marketplace at the Los Angeles Times 3rd Annual Investment Strategies Conference, Los Angeles, CA, May 23, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Remarks: An Essential Next Step in the Evolution of Corporate Governance at the Audit Committee Symposium, New York, N. Y., June 29, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Remarks to the President's Council on Year 2000 Conversion, Financial Sector Group Year 2000 Summit, Washington, DC, September 17, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Remarks: Dynamic Markets, Timeless Principles at Columbia Law School, New York, NY, September 23, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Remarks: Corporate Governance in a Global Arenato the American Council on Germany, New York, NY, October 7, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Remarks to the Panel on Audit Effectiveness of the Public Oversight Board, Public Oversight Hearings, New York, N. Y., October 7, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Remarks at the Municipal Market Roundtable, SEC Headquarters, Washington, DC, October 14, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Remarks: Financial Self-Defense: Tips From an SEC insider at the Boston Globed MoneymattersPersonal Finance Conference, Boston, MA, October 16, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Remarks: Quality Information: The Lifeblood of Our Markets at the Economic Club of New York, New York, NY, October 18, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Remarks on Proposals Concerning Mergers and Acquisitions, SEC Headquarters, Washington, DC, October 19, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Remarks: Best Execution: Promise of Integrity, Guardian of Competitionto the Securities Industry Association, Boca Raton, FL, November 4, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Remarks: Common Sense Investing in the 21st Century Marketplace at Investor's Town Meeting, Albuquerque, NM, November 20, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Remarks: Common Sense Investing in the 21st Century Marketplace at Investor's Town Meeting, New York, NY, December 9, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Remarks: Investing With Your Eyes Open at the Los Angeles Times 4th Annual Investment Strategies Conference, Los Angeles, CA, February 12, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Remarks to the Mutual Fund Directors Education Council Conference, Washington, DC, February 17, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Remarks: The New Economyat The Finance Conference 2000, Boston College, Boston, MA, March 6, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Remarks: Visible Prices, Accessible Markets, Order Interaction at the Northwestern University School of Law, Kellogg Graduate School of Management, March 16, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Remarks: Best Execution, Price Transparency and Linkages: Protecting the Investor Interest at the Washington University School of Law, March 24, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Opening Statement: Amendments to Form ADVat the Open Commission Meeting, Washington, DC, April 5, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Remarks at the Economic Club of Washington, April 6, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Remarks at the Annual Options Industry Conference, Palm Beach, FL, May 5, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Remarks: Renewing the Covenant With Investors at the New York University Center for Law and Business, New York, NY, May 10, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Remarks to the Panel on Audit Effectiveness,, New York, NY, July 10, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Remarks: Investing With Your Eyes Open at the SEC Investors Town Meeting, Cleveland, OH, July 25, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Opening Statement to the US SEC Open Meeting on Market Structure Initiatives in the Options Market and Public Disclosure of Order Routing Practices and Execution Quality, July 25, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Opening Statement to the US SEC Open Meeting on Regulation Fair Disclosure, August 10, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Remarks: Investing With Your Eyes Open at The Washington Post Investors Town Meeting, Washington, DC, September 16, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Remarks: A Profession at the Crossroads before the National Association of State Boards of Accountancy, Boston, MA, September 18, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Remarks on the 60th Anniversary of the Investment Company Act and the Investment Company Institute, October 5, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Remarks: Toward Markets Driven by Footsteps at the 67th Annual Conference and Business Meeting of the Security Traders Association, Boca Raton, FL, October 12, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Remarks before the National Conference of CPA Practitioners, Great Neck, NY, October 20, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Remarks: The Public's Profession at the Fall Council of the American Institute of Certified Public Accountants (AICPA), Las Vegas, NV, October 24, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Remarks: Costs Paid With Other People's Moneyat the A. A. Sommer Lectureship, Fordham Law School, New York, NY, November 3, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Remarks before the 2000 Annual Meeting, Securities Industry Association, Boca Raton, FL, November 9, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Opening Statement to the US SEC Open Meeting on Market Structure Initiatives in the Options and Equities Markets, and Rules Governing Auditor Independence, November 15, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Remarks before the Forum Club of Southwest Florida. Introduction attached. Naples, FL, December 1, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Remarks at the Conference on the Rise and Effectiveness of New Corporate Governance Standards, Federal Reserve Bank of New York, New York, NY, December 12, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Announcement of Levitt's Resignation, US SEC, Washington, DC, December 19, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - The National Market System: A Vision That Endures at Stanford University, Stanford, CA, January 8, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Opening Statement: The NASD's Proposed SuperMontage and Streamlining the SEC's Process of Reviewing Filings by Self Regulatory Organizations before the US SEC Open Meeting, Washington, DC, January 10, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Testimonies' Index, 1993 - 2000 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Subseries III.2: Congressional Testimonies
    Computer printouts of Congressional Testimonies by Arthur Levitt Jr. as SEC chairman
    - Statement of Arthur Levitt, Before the Senate Committee on Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs, concerning his nomination to be a member of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission, July 13, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Before the Senate Subcommittee on Securities, Committee on Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs, re: Authorization Request for Fiscal Years 1994-1995 (oral and written), July 29, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Before the House Subcommittee on Telecommunications and Finance, Committee on Energy and Commerce, re: Investment Company Industry, August 4, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Before the House Subcommittee on Telecommunications and Finance, Committee on Energy and Commerce, re: the State of the Municipal Securities Market, September 9, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Before the Senate Subcommittee on Securities, Committee on Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs, re: the Investment Company Industry, November 10, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Before the House Subcommittee on Oversight and Investigations committee on Energy and Commerce re: Proposed Merger between Mellon Bank Corporation and Dreyfus Corporation and related functional regulation issues, March 2, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Before the House Subcommittee on Commerce, Justice, and State, the Judiciary and related agencies, Committee on Appropriations, re: Appropriations for Fiscal Year 1995, March 16, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Before the House Committee on Banking, Finance and Urban Affairs, re: Hedge Fund Activities in the US Financial Markets (oral and written), April 13, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Before the House Subcommittee on Telecommunications and Finance, Committee on Energy and Commerce, re: H.R. 3447, (oral and written), April 14, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Before Senate Subcommittee on Commerce, Justice, and State, the Judiciary and related agencies, Committee on Appropriations, re: Appropriations for Fiscal Year 1995, May 5, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Before the Senate Subcommittee on Securities Committee on Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs, re: Central Bank of Denver Decision, May 12, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Before the House Subcommittee on Telecommunications and Finance, Committee on Energy and Commerce, re: Derivative Financing Instruments, May 25, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Before the House Subcommittee on Telecommunications and Finance, Committee on Energy and Finance, re: Litigation Under TI-IF, Federal Securities Laws, July 22, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Before House Subcommittee on Telecommunications and Finance, Committee on Energy and Commerce, re: Commission's recent efforts to combat sales practice abuses in the securities industry (oral and written), September 14, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Before the Senate Committee on Banking, Housing and Urban Affairs, re: International Markets and Individual Investors, September 18, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Before the House Subcommittee on Telecommunications and Finance, Committee on Energy and Commerce, re: Regulation of the Investment Company Industry, September 27, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Before the Senate Committee on Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs, re: International Markets and Individual Investors, September 28, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Before the Senate Committee on Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs, re:Municipal Bond and Government Securities Markets (oral and written), January 5, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Before the House Committee on Commerce, re: The Municipal Securities Market, January 12, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Before U.S. House of Representatives, re:Litigation Reform Proposals (oral and written), February 10, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Before U.S. House of Representatives, re:The Financial Services Competitiveness Act of 1995And Related Issues (oral and written), March 15, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Before the Subcommittee on Capital, Markets, Securities and Government sponsored enterprises, Committee on Banking and Financial, re: Markets and Trading Reorganization and Reform Act, March 30, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Before House Subcommittee on Commerce, Justice, and State, the Judiciary and related agencies, Committee on Appropriations, re: Appropriations for Fiscal Year 1996, April 4, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Before the Senate Subcommittee on Securities, Committee on Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs, re:Litigation Reform Proposals (oral and written), April 6, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Before U.S. House of Representatives, Testimony on H.R. 1062, The Financial Services Competitiveness Act of 1995(oral and written), June 6, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Before the Subcommittee on Telecommunications and Finance, Committee on Commerce, U.S. House of Representatives, Oral Statement re:PUCHA, August 4, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Before the House Committee on Commerce, Subcommittees on Telecommunications and Finance and Energy and Power, re: The Public Utility Holding Company Act of 1935, August 4, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Before the Subcommittee on Telecommunications and Finance, Committee on Commerce, U.S. House of Representatives, re:H.R. 2131, The Capital Markets Deregulation and Liberalization Act of 1995,(oral and written)., November 30, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Before the Subcommittee on Telecommunications and Finance, Committee on Commerce, U.S. House of Representatives, re:the Commission's Authorization Request for Fiscal Year 1997 (oral and written)., February 28, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Before the House of Representatives re:Appropriations for Fiscal Year 1997 (oral and written). May 9, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Before the Senate Committee on Banking, Housing and Urban Affairs, re: S1815, the Securities Investment Promotion Act (oral and written)., June 5, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Before the House of Representatives on S1815, June 5, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Before the Subcommittee on Financial Institutions and Consumer Credit of the Committee on Banking and Financial Services, U.S. House of Representatives, re:H.R. 268, The Depository Institution Affiliation and Thrift Charter Conversion Act,(oral and written), February 13, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Before the House Commerce Subcommittee on Finance and Hazardous Materials, re:SEC Reauthorization, March 6, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Before the House Appropriations Subcommittee on Commerce, Justice, and State, the Judiciary, and Related Agencies, re:Appropriations for Fiscal Year 1998, March 14, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Before the House Appropriations Subcommittee on Commerce, Justice, and State, the Judiciary, and Related Agencies, re:the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission's Appropriations for Fiscal Year 1998, March 19, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Before the Committee on Banking and Financial Services, U.S. House of Representatives, re: Financial Modernization, May 22, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Before the Committee on Commerce, Subcommittee on Financial and Hazardous Materials, U.S. House of Representatives,re:Financial Modernization and H.R. 10, The Financial Services Competition Act of 1997, July 17, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Before the Senate Banking Subcommittee on Securities, re:the Impact of the Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995, July 24, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Before the Subcommittee on Financial Services and Technology of the Committee on Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs, U.S. Senate, re:the Readiness of the United States Securities Industry and Public Companies To Meet the Information Processing Challenges of the Year 2000, July 30, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Before the Senate Governmental Affairs Permanent Subcommittee on Investigations re: Micro CapMarket (NOTE: text corrected 10-03-97), September 22, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Before the Subcommittee on Capital Markets, Securities and Government Sponsored Enterprises re: FASB's Proposed Accounting Rules for Derivative Financial Contracts, October 1, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Before the House Commerce Subcommittee on Finance and Hazardous Materials, re: The Implementation of the Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995, October 21, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Before the Senate Banking Subcommittee on Securities, re: S. 1260, the Securities Litigation Uniform Standards Act of 1997, October 29, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Before the Subcommittee on Securities, Committee on Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs, re: Circuit Breakers, January 29, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Before the Subcommittee on Commerce, Justice, State and Judiciary of the House Committee on Appropriations, re: Appropriations for Fiscal Year 1999 (oral and written)., March 18, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Before the Subcommittee on Commerce, Justice, State and Judiciary of the Senate Committee on Appropriations, re: Appropriations for Fiscal Year 1999 (oral and written)., March 19, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Before the Senate Committee on Banking, Housing and Urban Affairs, re: Nomination, March 25, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Before the Subcommittee on Finance and Hazardous Materials, House Committee on Commerce re: H.R. 1689, The Securities Litigation Uniform Standards Act of 1997(NOTE: text corrected 05-22-98), May 19, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Before the Senate Committee on Banking, Housing and Urban Affairs, re: Modernizing the Laws That Govern Our Financial Services Industry, June 25, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Before the Senate Committee on Agriculture, Nutrition, and Forestry re: The Regulation of the Over-the-Counter Derivatives Market and Hybrid Instruments, July 30, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Before the House Subcommittee on Finance and Hazardous Materials re: Transparency in the United States Debt Market and Mutual Fund Fees and Expenses, September 29, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Before the Senate Committee on Banking, Housing and Urban Affairs re: Financial Modernization Legislation, February 24, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Before the House Subcommittee on Finance and Hazardous Materials, Committee on Commerce, re: Transparency in the United States Corporate Debt Market, March 18, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Before the Senate Subcommittee on Securities, Committee on Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs, re: Fee Collections, March 24, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Before the Senate Subcommittee on Commerce, Justice, State and the Judiciary of the Committee on Appropriations, re: Appropriations for Fiscal Year 2000, March 25, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Before the Subcommittee on Commerce, Justice, State and the Judiciary of the Committee on Appropriations, U.S. House of Representatives, re: Appropriations for Fiscal Year 2000 (oral and written), April 14, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Before the House Committee on Commerce, re: H. R. 10 The Financial Services Act of 1999, May 5, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 2)